I will put more light on this sticker
because I was praying and saying to God, let me put a cross, just a cross.
The Lord said, "Put your picture there".
I keep asking God, "Why my picture?"
He said, "Yes, people need the grace to dream
dreams and to see visions".
Let love lead.
The rule in this is that you must love.
You must love your neighbour as yourself.
Love God above all.
If you can do that, no one can stand against you.
People will try it.
You have a battle. You may come out with bruises but you will overcome!
Amen!
You will overcome.
Now, don't just use one hand to collect it.
Collect it because you are collecting fire.
The New Anointing Sticker
Christ's workers sent by the Lord's servant Prophet T.B. Joshua
moved throughout the auditorium of the SCOAN,
sharing the new Anointing Sticker to the people in the name of Jesus and the blood of Jesus.
When the people started receiving the new Anointing Sticker,
hundreds fell under the healing and delivering power of the blood of Jesus and the fire of the Holy Ghost.
The impact was evident all over the auditorium
as people that were held captive by evil spirits were exposed and delivered in Jesus' name.
In the book of Acts we read about how God Almighty used different mediums to express Himself.
Anything that had came in contact with Apostle Paul was taken to the sick and demon possessed
and they were healed and delivered. As it was then, so it is today.
The book of Acts is not mere history but a pattern of what Jesus Christ wants His church to be today.
His healing, delivering and saving grace has not stopped just because He is no longer visible in our midst.
In fact, it is even greater because Jesus can be at places at all times by His spirit.
Hundreds of people that were afflicted with sicknesses and diseases also vomited out
all the poisonous substances within their bodies
and they were healed when they received the new Anointing Sticker.
If there is anyone here that is trying to avoid this sticker,
because once you have this sticker, you are under the influence of God Almighty.
If there is anyone that was avoiding this sticker while they were giving it out - right now, Holy Ghost fire!
I rebuke you, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever you are!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits After Receiving The Anointing Sticker
Hundreds all over the auditorium that avoided the new Anointing Sticker
fell under the anointing of Jesus Christ as Prophet T.B. Joshua declared Holy Ghost fire
to consume whatever that was not of God in the peoples' lives.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits After Receiving The Anointing Sticker
You people should stop.
I will talk! You people should stop!
I will talk.
I'm from the water.
You said what?
Please, I will not come again. Please allow me go.
You will not come here again?
Allow me to go, I won't come again.
Please leave me now!
Your presence is biting me.
My body.
Have you been watching Emmanuel TV?
Yes.
When my mother came here, you delivered her, and she left.
I decided to come. I wanted to leave when
you started distributing the anointing sticker.
My body is itching me.
You have delivered many of my people, I don't want you to continue again.
My name is Charity Omero. I'm from
Abia State, Nigeria.
I am 19 years old.
The woman standing next to me is my mom.
My mom was a queen in my kingdom
while I was a princess.
When she left the kingdom, everybody in the kingdom was annoyed.
They wanted her back by all means, but the prayer of the wise men couldn't allow her to come back.
So they decided that I should go,
saying that I should either kill Wise Man Daniel, Prophet T.B. Joshua or my mom.
I love my mom so much, that I didn't want to kill her.
So I decided to take the risk to come and kill Wise Man Daniel and Prophet T.B. Joshua.
When I came inside the church I had four powers.
Two in my hand, one in my eye, and the other one in my private part.
Whenever I travelled to my kingdom,
my upper body would be like a human being, while waist down would be like a snake.
So with the power in my eye, if I looked at you,
you wouldn't get yourself again.
My hand was poisonous. Any drink or glass cup I touched was poisoned.
If I couldn't get you through this, my last hope was by showing my nakedness.
If you saw me naked, you would be attracted to me and you would fall for me.
When I came inside the church,
my plan was that
I would waive my hand and all the electricity would go off.
I would make everyone in the church go to sleep.
Then I would come to the alter, tear the man of God's clothes and my own.
Then either he would do what I told him or if he refused,
I would wake everyone up and seeing that, they would not believe that he was a true man of God.
Through that, I would have damaged his name.
I have destroyed so many men of God and people around me.
Most of these men of God, if they came to pray for me in my house, I would look straight into their eyes.
Instead of them preaching the word of God, they would turn around and say other things like,
"Come, let's go out. Where are we going to drink?"
I would start laughing at them.
I would say, "Look at these people!"
Later they will say that they are praising God and that they don't know what they are doing.
I did many things, especially to men of God because they are the ones tying us down.
When I came to the church, that was my plan for the man of God.
I tried waving my hand several times to stop the electricity, but it would not go off,
When I tried to do it to Prophet T.B. Joshua, I found out that this man was too strong.
I tried and tried, but it was not working for me.
I was angry, so I went outside.
As I went outside, I didn't know what pushed me inside the church again
saying, "Come on, will you go back!"
I came inside angrily and immediately I wanted to sit down, one of the ushers gave me this sticker.
I didn't know whether I was to hold the sticker, throw it on the floor or reject it.
I collected the sticker.
When I took it, my hand became hot as if fire was all over my hands.
My hand was catching fire. It was as if someone gave me fire to hold for him or her.
I was hot from my hands, to my fingers, all over
my body, my hair and inside me.
I felt like tearing my clothes, I wanted them to bring me water to pour over me,
too see if it would cool down but it was
too much for me to withstand it.
I couldn't take it. I opened my handbag to put the Anointing Sticker inside.
After I put it inside, I was still holding my handbag.
But I couldn't even drop my handbag on the floor, so I took it out again.
I then put it on the chair, thinking that would stop it but the fire was still burning all over me.
I didn't know what to do. I fell down.
I was delivered through the Anointing Sticker and the prayers of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I would sleep when I felt like it was time to go to our meetings.
I would sleep like someone who was dead.
If anyone would move close to me
and accidentally touch me,
I would die and not come back.
Therefore when I wanted to sleep, I would sleep alone.
These things had been happening
to me since my childhood.
My mom was not with me.
She was out of the country, while
I was alone with my brothers.
All of us, including my bothers, were from the same kingdom.
My mom was a queen in our kingdom,
while I was the princess.
She too was delivered in this church.
My mom was delivered from the spirit of water snake.
When the man of God was praying, a snake was inside me.
It was as if my stomach just opened and the snake just came out and
when the man of God said, "Holy Ghost Fire,"
I saw the snake running out of the church and I was delivered.
Since then, I have had no dream
or attack. I am free!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Wise Man Daniel valiantly removes the generational curses and demonic authorities
that are behind their failings and setbacks.
He continues throughout the congregation and encounters this woman.
She begins to manifest.
Who are you?
Daniel, I am the queen of all queens.
What have you done to her?
Daniel, you should know all these things.
You know, I cannot open up.
This is the arena of liberty,
Jesus is more than you.
What have you done to her?
Let me ease myself first before I can talk.
What have you done to her before...
I am the queen of all queens and you know it.
Speak out! What have you done to her?
You know I'm the queen.
What have you done to her?
I have destroyed her.
In what way?
Daniel, you know.
Speak out!
I will not!
I can't.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Come out of this body, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Watch your screen.
This is a manifestation of the evil spirit.
Right now, she is not at ease with herself.
You are free. Rise up.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
What happened to you?
Open your eyes.
Am I drunk?
What happened to you?
What are you doing here?
I'm not doing anything here. Nothing.
Nothing?
Yes!
So, you have forgotten that
you have been abusing me.
I can't abuse you.
But you said you are the queen of the
coast.
I can't be the queen of the coast.
Thank you, Lord. You are free.
Thank you. I'm sorry, Prophet.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Praise the Lord! Emmanuel!
(Matthew 1:23 - God is with us)
My name is Mrs Rita Ignatius Omero.
I'm a Nigerian living in Gabon.
What happened last week was that I came here
for the normal Sunday worship.
I didn't come for any deliverance.
I was there when the man of God, Wise Man Daniel, came to me and he laid hands on me.
Before I knew it, the contrary spirit within me started manifesting confessing that I was a queen of queens.
This queen of queens all started in 2003, when I gave birth to my son.
I knew that I had a contrary spirit because
I was going from one church to another for deliverance.
There was even one church I went to in Gabon.
When they were in the deliverance section, and
it reached my turn,
the man of God laid hands on me,
and the contrary spirit in me gripped the man.
I wanted to strangle the man of God.
If it wasn't for the workers in the church,
I don't know what would have happened.
I hit the man of God and beat him mercilessly.
Even the man of God came the next day to my husband,
and asked him,
"How long have you been living with this woman?"
He said, "Please, sir, I don't want your wife coming to my church for deliverance again
because last night, the contrary spirit nearly finished my household".
That is how I stopped, but it continued.
Even when I slept in the night, my husband would lay his hands on me and pray for me.
When I woke up and saw him praying for me, the spirit in me would start manifesting.
At times my tongue would come out long like a snake.
My husband would run away and call the pastors.
When they came, everything would be settled and my husband would be embarrassed.
This thing was happening in my life all these years.
One day my son woke up in the morning and said,
"Mummy, please I don't want to call you by your name. I want to call you 'my queen'".
That was how he started calling me 'my queen'.
At a time, he stopped calling me 'my queen' and started calling me 'queen of all queens'.
Everywhere I went, people would call me 'queen of all queens'.
I did not know there was something attached to this 'queen of all queens' till last Sunday.
My husband has been passing through this all these years.
This thing has caused me sicknesses and has set my husband back.
Whenever my husband got a contract to work, he worked off shore.
Whenever they called
him for an appointment,
due to this contrary spirit, whenever my husband showed his face, they would reject my husband.
At times I would fight my husband when he was going to church.
Whenever I would have a problem with my husband, the contrary spirit within me would beat my husband.
One time they beat my husband, and he could not turn his neck for four days.
Now you beat.
Because you are delivered, that's why you are saying that.
We agree that it was a contrary spirit.
Now you beat your husband.
Yes, sir.
Until last week, by the grace of God, I came here for a normal Sunday service.
God used Wise Man Daniel
to deliver me.
Since last week, I've been sleeping well. I don't
hear the sound of snakes anymore.
I don't have the fear of snakes anymore.
I don't have in mind that I will see snakes
everywhere I am going.
I'm free. I sleep well!
I thank God! Emmanuel!
Where is your husband?
My husband is in Gabon.
Your husband is now a husband.
There is a wonderful name Jesus
There is no other name I know
You may be seated, thank you.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Rita Ignatius.
I'm from Nigeria but living in Gabon.
The girl beside me is my daughter,
Charity Ignatius.
She was a princess in my kingdom.
My brethren, I thank God for today. I thank God
for what he has done in my family .
Many of you think that it's just a joke. It is not a joke.
I don't know how to start.
When the man of God was asking me to open up,
I said that I didn't want to open up
because I knew the reason.
I knew that my daughter would come back to fight for me.
It all happened when I came to The SCOAN
last year in April.
When I came, Wise Man Daniel
touched me.
Wise Man Daniel provoked me.
The spirit in me was wildly provoked.
As God had it, he asked me a question,
"Who are you?"
I said, "I am the queen of all queens". And that was what I was.
Not a queen but queen of all queens; I controlled.
When he asked me, I didn't want to open up
because I knew where I was coming from
and I knew the disaster that would follow after my deliverance.
I stood on my words as I didn't want to open up.
I knew that my family would come for me.
Finally, the man of God, Wise Man Daniel, delivered me.
When he delivered me, I received a call
that my daughter was misbehaving at home.
I gave birth to them physically and spiritually.
When I travelled back to Gabon last week, I was watching Emmanuel TV because I didn't go to church.
I was feeling dizzy and said, "Let me pray with Emmanuel TV".
I was there when I saw my daughter. I said, "This girl resembles my daughter!"
I said, "Wow, God created two identical people in the world".
I said, "No, how can this girl resemble my daughter?"
She was wearing my daughter's earrings,
and I bought those clothes.
She has her own, and I have my own.
I said, "No! My daughter cannot come to The SCOAN without telling me!"
When I ran out because I was not
feeling comfortable, I phoned.
Somebody picked up her phone and said that it was my daughter that was manifesting there.
Myself - heat!
As I was breathing, I vibrated.
That was how I came down. I thank God
for delivering my family.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.